pennypop.com 2004-06-06

# iLoanDirect.com :: Privacy Policy

|  | 

Privacy Policy 

We realize and respect the importance of your information security and your personal privacy. With your permission, we use information about you plus information you provide to help find solutions that meet your needs.   
By using our Website(s) and submitting online information about yourself, you are indicating that you allow us to use your information as described below. Where Information is Gathered About You. We may gather information about you from: You're the completion of the online form, or other information that you provide to us or our affiliates, such as your name, address and other information; Our affiliates that provide us with information about you from consumer reporting agencies, unless you request that your information not be shared; Companies that provide consumer data or analysis as a service or product.   
We may gather information on your online activity on our Website(s) or those of our affiliates to help us improve our Websites or to track your site navigation so that we can understand your preferences and enhance our offerings and performance. 

Protection of your information To keep your personal information strictly confidential, we protect it with physical and electronic safeguards, and we make sure that we abide by applicable federal security standards. 

In addition, we require all outside firms and agencies we do business with, to maintain the confidentiality of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and to comply with all applicable laws. 

Security We take every precaution to protect our user's information. If you are ordering from us over the internet, we ensure the security of your credit card information. When you submit your information online it is protected on one of our secured servers using SSL encryption (performance with Web TV cannot be guaranteed). Links This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of those sites. Please use your best judgment and read the privacy policy of each website that collects information about you. 

Opt-Out Notice We work with selected partners to offer you additional products and services that we think you may want. We will also forward your information to a maximum of three mortgage lenders. If you are a former customer, we maintain the confidentiality of your information as if you were still a customer.   
If you wish to not participate in any future offers, you may "Opt Out" -- that is, you may direct us not to forward your information to our affiliates and partners. 

Contact Us If you have any question about or privacy policy, please email us at [info@iloandirecte.com ](mailto:info@lendxpress.com)

|
